[{"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/菜篮子.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/柜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/饮料瓶.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/皮箱 .svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/铅笔_2.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 1, 3, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/菜篮子.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/门.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/油笔棒.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/寿司_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [3, 1, 2, 1], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/筛子.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/油笔棒.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/饼干盒.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 1, 2, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/魔方.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/柜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/铅笔_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/时钟.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 2, 2, 1], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/微波炉.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/铅笔_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/饮料瓶.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 1, 3, 1], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/魔方.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/饼干盒.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 1, 3], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/微波炉.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_3.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/冰箱.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 2, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/筛子.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/微波炉.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/时钟.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/皮鼓.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 2, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/皮箱 .svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/寿司_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/冰箱.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/微波炉.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 1, 1, 3], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_3.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/冰箱.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/手机.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/音响.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/饮料瓶.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 1, 2, 3], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/字母.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/门.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/饼干盒.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_3.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 2, 1, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/日历.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/汽水瓶.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/胶水.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 1, 2, 3], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/魔方.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/皮箱 .svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/油笔棒.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/柜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/字母.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 2, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/字母.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/冰箱.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/烧杯_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/微波炉.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/箱子_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/箱子.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 1, 3], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_3.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/盒子_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/饮料瓶.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/保险箱.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/瑜伽垫.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/书本_1.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 1, 2, 3], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/字母.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/皮箱 .svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/寿司_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/筛子.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/门.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_2.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 2, 2], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/魔方.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/门.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/饮料瓶.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/饼干盒.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/保险箱.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [2, 1, 1, 3], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-input", "title": "填一填", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "unit": "个", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/长方体/微波炉.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/正方体/积木_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/胶水.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/圆柱体/手电筒_1.svg"}], "typeList": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/球体_8.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体_5.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体-2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体_7.svg"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 3, 1], "resource": "resource", "explain": "explain", "knowledges": ["5以内 的数、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-6-5-04"}]